Solving a crime can be dirty work
Cleaner is a crime, thriller, mystery film directed by Renny Harlin.
Single father and former cop Tom Cutler has an unusual
occupation: he cleans up death scenes.
But when he's called in to sterilize a wealthy suburban residence after a brutal shooting, Cutler is shocked to
learn he may have unknowingly erased crucial evidence, entangling himself in a dirty criminal cover-up.
Tom Cutler, played by Samuel L. Jackson.
Eddie Lorenzo, played by Ed Harris.
Ann Norcut, played by Eva Mendes.
Det. Jim Vargas, played by Luis Guzmán.
Rose Cutler, played by Keke Palmer.
Cherie, played by Maggie Lawson.
Cleaner is a 2007 American thriller film directed by Renny Harlin.
It stars Samuel L.
Jackson as a crime scene cleaner who thinks he has become part of a
cover-up; Ed Harris, Keke Palmer, and Eva Mendes also star.
The film was released on May 27, 2007.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.